# KENNEDY OFOEZIE

ADDRESS: No. 4 Olori Oguntade Street, Ikosi Ketu, Lagos, Lagos state.

PHONE: +234 (0) 816 302 7032, +234 (0) 812 386 7962

EMAIL: ofoeziekennedy91@gmail.com

LinkedIn Profile: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/kennedy-ofoezie-917b3a179">www.linkedin.com/in/kennedy-ofoezie-917b3a179</a>

#### **SUMMARY**

Imaginative and diligent graphic designer with experience, exceptional attention to details and passion for delivering projects on time. Good time-management and problem-solving skills, knowledgeable in designing software such as Illustrator, Photoshop, and CorelDraw. I desire to be a visionary person who can rise up to take on challenges, with will power and determination to excel, and also to add positive values to the life of my colleagues and others.

#### **EDUCATION**

BA Accounting and Finance | Plymouth University, UK 2014 – 2017

- Major: Accounting and Finance
- Related Course work: Economics, Accounting and financial reporting, Corporate Finance

WASSCE | Christ Ambassador's College, Kaduna, Nigeria 2003 – 2009

- Major: Science department
- Related Course work: Biology, Chemistry, Physics, Further Mathematics

First School Leaving Certificate | Betty Queen Int'l School, Kaduna, Nigeria 1997 – 2003

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Freelance Graphic Designer | Lagos, Nigeria

- Designed Instagram Posts, Facebook Post, and any social media designs
- Designed business/complimentary cards, Birthday cards etc.
- Designed logos for businesses, branding and Packaging.
- Design mock ups with Adobe Photoshop.

Intern Ui/Ux Designer | Softcity Group, Lagos, Nigeria SEP 2019 - FEB 2020

- Designed mockups for both mobile and desktop applications using Figma.
- Designed UML documentation using StarUML.
- Scripted functional requirements for a Hospital Management System.

### (NYSC)Teacher | Bright kids Academy, Abia State, Nigeria JAN 2018 – JAN 2019

- Taught JSS1 SS1 Mathematics, Economics, Civic Education
- Physical Education

## Sales Representative | N20, Plymouth, UK JUN 2016 – JUN 2017

- Supervised marketing and sales of business brands.
- Engaged in clientele communication.
- Advertising and marketing.
- Supervised teams to market products.

# Library Assistant | Camosun college, Victoria Island, Canada May 2013 – September 2013

- Assisted in IT maintenance
- Peer review in course works: essays, research reports, and mathematics

### Management Skills

- Analytical thinking
- Good oral and written communication skills
- Ability to work as part of the team
- Accuracy and eye ball for details
- Computer literate.

### Technical Skills

- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- CorelDraw
- HTML5
- CSS
- InDesign

#### REFREE

### Alexander Chinwuba

- Nigerian Airspace Management Agency
- 08166369780

### Engr. Gilbert Obiajulu

- NNPC-KRPC LTD, Kaduna State
- 08036290430